gistplanet.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy 

Privacy Policy for www.gistplanet.com 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **kaymediacash@gmail.com. **

At www.gistplanet.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.  
This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.gistplanet.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.gistplanet.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends,  
administer the site, track users movement  
around the site, and gather demographic  
information. IP addresses, and other such  
information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**_Cookies and Web Beacons_**

www.gistplanet.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**_DoubleClick DART Cookie_**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.gistplanet.com.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it  
to serve ads to your users based on their visit  
to www.gistplanet.com and other sites on the  
Internet. 

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART  
cookie by visiting the Google ad and content  
network privacy policy at the following URL -  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   
* Google Adsense  
* Ad-Dynamo

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.gistplanet.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies  
( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize  
the advertising content that you see. 

www.gistplanet.com has no access to or  
control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy  
policies of these third-party ad servers for  
more detailed information on their practices as  
well as for instructions about how to opt-out  
of certain practices. www.gistplanet.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

****

****

## Get Updates Directly to your email
